Congratulations
to everybody around the room. It's an
honor to be sitting amongst achievers.
Congratulations on your results in 2025
KYC. Know your customer. Know your
company. Know you can
f
My biggest challenge is clearly to get
lead. Strategies to overcome this is
including number one asking for a
referral from my exiting client. Second
create by monthly events. Three and not
the least is that daily I add two new
names to my active contact list. MDRT is
important as a leader because it sets
the standard. Highquality people don't
follow average leader. They follow
results, discipline, and consistency.
MDRT to me is a symbol of trust. It
reflects the confidence my clients place
in me to guide them in making important
financial decisions for their lives and
families.
>> MDRT has taught me deep empathy. Behind
every number is a heavy responsibility.
is a silent promise I make to my
clients. It means I have both the
capability and the duty to be their safe
harbor. MDRT is not to be the best in
the world but to be the best for the
world. Persistency is the key when you
want to do MDRT. When you maintain a
good persistency, your first year
premium will be sustained and you will
continuously doing my MDRT.
MDRT is not just a target. It is a
standard of professionalism and
consistency. Lifetime MDRT is a result
of discipline, purpose and compromising
on the value I deliver.
MDRT is not just a target. It's a
standard that I set for myself to
performing in the highest level and be
the best version of myself in the
industry.
>> My MDRT achievement last year was driven
by a simple but powerful ABC method. A
accountability, B consistency, C
commitment. At this level, results don't
come from luck. They come from standard
that I refuse to lower.